Seitz, Peter Arbitration Files 5733
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Peter Seitz Arbitration Files
1954-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seitz, Peter
5733
24 cubic feet
24 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Collective labor agreements and correspondence
3338484
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 30, 1986
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Scope and Contents
These arbitration files are coded to indicate what is included in the file: TR = Transcript(s) B = Brief EX = Exhibit(s) AN = Arbitrator's Notes RC = Routine Correspondence A = Agreement SD = Supporting Document(s)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5588: David L. Cole Papers 5775: NAA Records 5970: Ralph Seward Additional Papers 6004: NAA Additional Records
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; Seitz, Peter, 1905-1983; Armco Steel Corporation; Allis-Chalmers Corporation; Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation; Anheuser-Busch, Inc.; ARCO Petroleum Products Co.; Atlantic Independent Union; Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania; Bethlehem Steel Company; Chandler Evans, Inc.; Columbia Broadcasting System, inc.; Continental Can Company; Curtiss-Wright Corporation; Delaware County Daily Times; Dupont; General Dynamics Corporation; General Electric Company; Greyhound Lines, Inc.; Inland Steel Company; Mack Trucks, inc.; Midwest Steel Co.; National Broadcasting Company; New York (N.Y.). Police Department; New York (N.Y.). Department of Social Services; New York City Transit Authority; New York Telephone Company; Newark Board of Education; Pennsylvania. Department of Public Welfare; Republic Steel Corporation; Republic Aviation Corporation; Trans World Airlines; United States Postal Service; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 300; United Steelworkers of America
3338484
- Abrams-Rubaloff and Associates vs. Cynthia Adler, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Issue: Rates of pay - commissions. (Award only).
- Acme Markets, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Local 1927., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Issue: Layoff. RC, B, AN, EX. (No award.)
- Aeronaves de Mexico, S.A. vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM)., 1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Issue: Absences - disciplinary. (Award only).
- Aerospace Division of Universal Oil vs. IAM, District 15., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  No award. RC, B.
- Air France vs. IAM, District 100, Air France vs. Edwin J. Papetti, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge, violation of plant rules. (Award only).
- Air France vs. Richard J. Morello., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge. B, EX, RC. (Award only).
- Allegheny County, Port Authority vs. Amalgamated Transit Union (ATU), Division 85., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Settled. RC, B.
- Allegheny County, Port Authority of vs. ATU, Division 85., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Issue: Theft - company property; discipline - discharge. TR, RC, B, AN, EX. (No award).
- Allegheny County, Port Authority of vs. ATU, Local 85., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Issue: Arbitrability - settled. RC, SD, EX, TR.
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), Local 1138, Local 1196, Local 2242, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. vs. USA, Local 1196, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - new equipment, added duties, seniority. (Award only).
- Allen Manufacturing Co. vs. International Union, United Automobile Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), Local 518, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  (No award). SD, AN, B, EX.
- Allied Gymnasium Equipment Co., Inc. vs. International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, Shopmen's Local 455, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Issue: Welfare Funds - Employer's contribution. (Award only).
- Allis-Chalmers Corp. (York, Pennsylvania Division) vs. IAM, Local 1400., 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Issue: Upgrading, assignment of jobs, management rights, demotions. (Award only).
- Allis-Chalmers Corp. (York, Pennsylvania Division) vs. IAM, Local 1400., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Issue: Overtime - assignment of jobs. B, A, AN, EX, RC.
- Allis-Chalmers Corp. (York, Pennsylvania Division) vs. IAM, Local 1400. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Issue: Bumping - seniority. B, AN, EX, RC.
- Altmann Bottling Co., Inc. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 1149., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Issue: Discipline - discharge. (Award only).
- American Airlines, Inc. vs. Air Line Pilots Association, International (ALPA)., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs seniority, Training and trial periods - refusal to grant. (Award only).
- American and National Leagues Professional Ball Clubs (ANLPBC) (San Diego Padres) vs. Major League Baseball Players Association (MLBPA) (Michael Corkins), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Issue: Default in payment, termination of contract; fringe benefits - travel pay. (Award only).
- ANLPBC (Montreal Expos and California Angels) vs. MLBPA (William H. Stoneman), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Issue: Contract interpretation - supplementary agreement. (Award only).
- ANLPBC (Oakland Athletics, Division of Charles O. Finley and Co., Inc.) vs. MLBPA (James A. "Catfish" Hunter), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Issue: Termination of contract; rates of pay - wage hold back. EX, SD, AN, RC.
- ANLPBC (Oakland Athletics, Division of Charles O. Finley and Co., Inc.) vs. MLBPA (James A. "Catfish" Hunter), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- ANLPBC (Oakland Athletics, Atlanta Braves) vs. MLBPA (Patrick Daniel Bouraque, Gary Gentry), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Issue: Termination of employment - severance pay.
- ANLPBC (San Diego Padres) vs. MLBPA (Glenn A. Beckeit), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Issue: Physical disability - rates of pay. (Award only).
- ANLPBC (Commissioner of Baseball) vs. MLBPA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Issue: Fringe benefits - travel pay. (Award only).
- ANLPBC (Minnesota Twins) vs. MLBPA, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ANLBPC (Atlanta Braves) vs. MLBPA (Paulino O. Casanova), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  Issue: Termination of contract; disability; fringe benefits - travel pay - room and board allowance. (Award only).
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Issue: Termination of contract; negotiations. RC, EX, SD, AN, TR.
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ANLPBC (Los Angeles Club and Montreal Club) vs. MLBPA (John A. Messersmith and David A. McNally), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Baseball Club vs. David McNally, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: Rates of Pay. RC, AN, EX, B. (No award).
- American Bakeries Co. vs. Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers Union, Local 50, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Settled. RC.
- American Bank Note Co. vs. Graphic Arts International Union, Local 119B-43B, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Withdrawn. RC, B, AN, TR.
- American Bosch Arma Corp. vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), Engineers Association of ARMA, Local 418, Local 464, 1956- 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs qualifications; Promotions seniority; Discipline refusal of overtime, violation of plant rules (sleeping on the job). (Award only).
- American Brass Co. (American Metal Hose Division vs. UAW, Local 1078; American Broadcasting Co. vs. Directors Guild of America, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - trainee assignments, Recall seniority, Contract interpretation rates of pay. (Award only).
- American Chain and Cable Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 4818, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension. (Award only).
- American Cyanamid Co. vs. International Chemical Workers Union (ICW), Local 111; vs. UMW, Local 12, 426; vs. ICW, Local 111, 1957-1977 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Issue: Supervisors - bargaining unit work - performance of; Assignment of jobs assignment of work outside unit; Contract interpretation unambiguous language; Contracting out layoff; Termination of employment following illness or physical disabilit
- American Machine and Foundry Co. vs. UAW, Local 116, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors; Layoff - recall. (Award only).
- American Smelting and Refining Co. vs. UAW, Local 143; vs. International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers - Perth Amboy Smelting and Refining Workers Union, Local 365, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Issue: Holidays and holiday pay layoff; Reinstatement - following illness or physical disability. (Award only).
- American Steel Foundries vs. USA, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems - new machinery. (Award only).
- American Stores Co. vs. Retail Store Employees Union Local 692, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Issue: Contract interpretation; supervisors and foremen - bargaining unit work - performance of. (Award only).
- American Telephone and Telegraph Co. (Long Lines Department) vs. Communication Workers of America (CWA), Local 2552, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - new jobs. (Award only).
- Ametek, Inc. (U.S. Gauge Division) vs. IAM, Bux-Mont Lodge 1092, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Issue: Overtime - rates of pay. (Award only).
- Amstar Corp. vs. Sugar Refinery Workers Union, Local 1650, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Issue: Reduction in Force - seniority. (Award only).
- Amstar Corp. (American Sugar Division) vs. ILA, Sugar Refinery Workers Union, Local 1650, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; insubordination discipline; discipline discharge; discipline suspension; fights and altercations assault on a fellow employee; assignment of jobs - seniority. (Award only).
- Anemostat Corp. of American vs. UAW, Local 1144, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Issue: Absences - excessive; discipline. (Award only).
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), National Conference of Brewery and Soft Drink Workers of the United States and Canada, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Issue: Grievance and grievance procedure - grievance committee meetings. (Award only).
- Anheuser-Busch, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 843, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Issue: Fights and altercations. (No award). RC, EX, TR, B.
- Ansonia Board of Education vs. Ansonia Federation of Teachers, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  Issue: Contract interpretation.
- ARCO Petroleum Products Co. vs. Atlantic Independent Union, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Issue: Grievance and grievance procedure - timeliness. B, RC, TR, EX, SD.
- ARCO Petroleum Products Co. vs. Atlantic Independent Union, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 1865, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. (Award only).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems. TR, EX. (No award).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors. TR. (No award).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Issue: Rates of pay; grievance and grievance procedure - timeliness. TR. (No award).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Issue: Schedules of work - shift scheduling. TR, SD. (No award).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Issue: Arbitration procedure - compliance with award. TR, SD, EX, AN.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Issue: Rates of pay - reporting pay. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Issue: Vacancies - seniority; bumping - bumping into specific job. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - past practice. TR, AN, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Issue: Seniority - past practice. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Issue: Schedules of work - seniority. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. TR, SD, AN.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Issue: Rates of pay. TR, SD, EX, AN.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Issue: Incentive pay and incentive systems - change in operations. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime. TR, SD, EX, AN.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Issue: Vacancies - temporary; vacancies - method of filling.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Issue: Schedules of work - notice. TR, AN, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Issue: Working conditions - safety. TR, AN, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Issue: Discipline - warnings. TR, AN, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Issue: Crew size - overtime. TR, SD. (No award).
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Issue: Posting. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Issue: Vacancies - temporary. TR, EX, RC.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Issue: Seniority - plant wide, departmental seniority.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Issue: Vacancies - seniority; bumping - training and trial periods. TR.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - physical qualifications; seniority. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Issue: Overtime - unscheduled overtime. TR, SD, EX, RC.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Issue: Seniority - vacancies. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors. TR, SD, EX, RC.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Issue: Discipline - refusal of overtime. TR, RC, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Issue: Working conditions - sanitary conditions. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Issue: Schedules of work - shift scheduling. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  Issue: Schedules of work - assignment of jobs. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Issue: Classification of jobs - upgrading.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  Issue: Overtime - seniority. TR, RC, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority; posting. TR, SD.
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 case B-63-184 (Box 3.1, Folder 9)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-3 (Box 3.1, Folder 18)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-63-186 (Box 3.1, Folder 17)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-63-175 (Box 3.1, Folder 16)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-63-90 (Box 3.1, Folder 15)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-136; B-64-202; B-64-137; B-64-153 (Box 3.1, Folder 14)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-06 // B-64-65 (Box 3.1, Folder 13)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-9 to 12 // B-64-15 to 20 (Box 3.1, Folder 12)
- United Steelworkers of America, Local 1865 and ARMCO Steel Corporation, 1956 (Box 3.1, Folder 1)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 case B-64-8 (Box 3.1, Folder 10)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-B-64-282 (Box 3.1, Folder 21)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 case B-64-186 (Box 3.1, Folder 8)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 case B-63-190//B-63-191 (Box 3.1, Folder 7)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 - case B-63-47 (Box 3.1, Folder 6)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 (Box 3.1, Folder 5)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation - Case B-99-61 - Group Grievance (Box 3.1, Folder 4)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation - Case B-81-61 (Box 3.1, Folder 3)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation - Case B-79-61 (Box 3.1, Folder 2)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-184 (Box 3.1, Folder 11)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-11 (Box 3.1, Folder 29)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-39 (Box 3.1, Folder 38)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-19; B-65-20 (Box 3.1, Folder 37)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-14 (Box 3.1, Folder 36)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-325; B-64-336; B-65-12, 13 (Box 3.1, Folder 35)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-324 (Box 3.1, Folder 34)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-7; 21; 41; 59; 75; 101; 136; 145; 170; 191 (Box 3.1, Folder 33)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-243 (Box 3.1, Folder 32)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-182; B-64-183 (Box 3.1, Folder 19)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-66-21 (Box 3.1, Folder 30)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-66-5 (Box 3.1, Folder 20)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-301 (Box 3.1, Folder 28)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-37 (Box 3.1, Folder 27)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-186; B-64-207 (Box 3.1, Folder 26)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-223; B-64-245 (Box 3.1, Folder 25)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-302; B-64-306; B-64-317 (Box 3.1, Folder 24)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-108; B-64-155 (Box 3.1, Folder 23)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-B-65-30 (Box 3.1, Folder 22)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-65-35, 46 (Box 3.1, Folder 39)
- ARMCO Steel Corporation and United SteelworkersLocal 3185 Grievance no. B-64-289 (Box 3.1, Folder 31)
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - overtime. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Issue: Seniority - Breaks in continuity; absences. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Issue: Overtime - absentee replacement; overtime - seniority. TR, SD, EX.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. TR.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Issue: Safety - protective clothing and equipment. TR, RC, SD, AN.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Issue: Vacation pay - computation. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - assignment of work outside unit. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8a)
  Issue: Lunch periods. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - shutdown. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Issue: Overtime - assignment of jobs; overtime - seniority. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Issue: Union representatives and business - pay for meetings.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Issue: Seniority - assignment of jobs. TR, B, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - added duties. TR, EX, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Issue: Transfers - seniority. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Issue: Assignment of jobs - seniority. TR, SD.
- Armco Steel Corp. (Baltimore, Maryland Works) vs. USA, Local 3185, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Issue: Discipline - suspension; discipline - negligence and carelessness. TR, SD, EX.